A Guide to the Department of Education, School Buildings Service, Architectural drawings and plans, 1920-1970
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Localities. (Box 1-10., Reel 1832-1837.)
  - Northampton - Exmore - Willis Wharf, April 1926 (Folder 5, Folder 7-L-16)
  - Northampton - Eastville, Sept 192- (Folder 5, Folder 7-L-17)
  - Northumberland - Heathville- Addition, Sept 194- (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-2)
  - Northumberland - Heathville- School Board Office Building, Sept 193- (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-2)
  - Northumberland - Reedville, July 192- (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-1)
  - Northumberland - Heathville, Aug 1934 (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-2)
  - Nottoway - Blackstone Elementary, May 1937 (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-3)
  - Nottoway - Nottoway Training- Addition, June 1929 (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-4)
  - Nottoway - Burkeville Repairs, May 1940 (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-4)
  - Nottoway - Burkeville- Home Economics Cottage, April 193- (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-4)
  - Nottoway - Vocational Shop, Oct 194- (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-4)
  - Orange - Unionville- Toilet Addition, Nov 1937 (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-7)
  - Orange - Unionville, March 192- (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-7)
  - Orange - Orange, April 193- (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-8)
  - Orange - School For Barboursville, Nov 1933 (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-6)
  - Orange - Gordonsville- Addition, May 192- (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-5)
  - Orange - School At Barboursville- Addition, May 1926 (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-6)
  - Orange - Barboursville- Addition, June 193- (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-6)
  - Page - Shenandoah, May 1928 (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-9)
  - Page - Springfield District Elementary, March 193- (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-10)
  - Patrick - Woolwine, July 1938 (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-13)
  - Patrick - Meadows of Dan, Oct 1936 (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-12)
  - Patrick - Hardin Reynolds Memorial- Addition, June 1935 (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-11)
  - Patrick - Stuart High School- Gymnasium & Shop, March 193- (Folder 5, Folder 7-R-11)
  - Pittsylvania - School For Brosville, Jan 1939 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-5)
  - Pittsylvania - Climax- Addition, May 1933 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-3)
  - Pittsylvania - Whitmell, June 1931 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-6)
  - Pittsylvania - Schoolfield- Addition, June 1933 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-8)
  - Pittsylvania - Brosville - 6 Room School, March 192- (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-5)
  - Pittsylvania - School for Chatham, Nov 1938 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-4)
  - Pittsylvania - School for Chatham, March 192- (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-4)
  - Pittsylvania - Climax- Addition, Feb 1939 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-3)
  - Pittsylvania - Climax- Home Economics Cottage Alterations, Aug 1933 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-3)
  - Pittsylvania - Dan River High School- Alterations, May 1937 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-7)
  - Pittsylvania - Spring Garden- Addition, Aug 1922 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-1)
  - Pittsylvania - Gretna- Gymnasium & Addition, May 1938 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-2)
  - Pittsylvania - Colored School For Gretna, Dec 1936 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-2)
  - Pittsylvania - School For Gretna, April 1931 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-2)
  - Pittsylvania - School For Gretna, Aug 1930 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-2)
  - Pittsylvania - Gretna, May 1924 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-2)
  - Pittsylvania - Spring Garden- Addition, Oct 1938 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-1)
  - Pittsylvania - Spring Garden- Addition, June 1926 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-1)
  - Pittsylvania - School For Spring Garden, June 1926 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-1)
  - Pittsylvania - Dan River, May 1931 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-7)
  - Pittsylvania - Climax, June 1924 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-3)
  - Powhatan - Powhatan Training School, Dec 1936 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-12)
  - Prince Edward - Darlington Heights- Addition, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-14)
  - Prince Edward - Darlington Heights- Addition, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-14)
  - Prince Edward - School For Worsham, June 192- (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-15)
  - Prince Edward - Worsham- Shop, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-15)
  - Prince Edward - Darlington Heights, 9 Room School & Auditorium, Feb 1926 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-14)
  - Prince Edward - County Training School, Sept 1938 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-17)
  - Prince Edward - Mercy Seat, May 192- (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-13)
  - Prince Edward - School For Rice, March 193- (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-16)
  - Prince Edward - Worsham- Addition, Apr 194- (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-13)
  - Prince Edward - Farmville High School- Addition, Jan 1939 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-13)
  - Prince Edward - 4 Room School & Auditorium, July 1925 (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-13)
  - Prince Edward - Green Bay, April 192- (Folder 6, Folder 8-L-13)
  - Prince George - Disputanta- Addition, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-1)
  - Prince George - Disputanta- Addition, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-1)
  - Prince George - Prince George Colored High School- Addition, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-1)
  - Prince George - Prince George Colored High School- Addition, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-1)
  - Prince George - Disputanta- Alterations & Additions, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-1)
  - Prince William - Antioch- Addition, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-4)
  - Prince William - Bennett-Addition, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-6)
  - Prince William - Gainesville District, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-6)
  - Prince William - Old Woodbine, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-5)
  - Prince William - Manassas, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-5)
  - Prince William - One Room School (Manassas), n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-5)
  - Prince William - Occoquan- Addition, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-3)
  - Prince William - Nokesville- Gymnasium, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-4)
  - Prince William - Dumfries, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-5)
  - Prince William - Occoquan, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-3)
  - Prince William - Occoquan- Addition, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-3)
  - Prince William - Occoquan District- Addition, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-3)
  - Prince William - Occoquan- Shop, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-3)
  - Prince William - Occoquan- Addition, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-3)
  - Prince William - Brentville District, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-4)
  - Pulaski - Temporary Kitchen, Feb 1942 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-9)
  - Pulaski - Pulaski High School - Locker Room Addition, March 194- (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-11)
  - Pulaski - Pulaski High School- Gymnasium Addition, May 1946 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-11)
  - Pulaski - Calfee Training, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-12)
  - Pulaski - Draper- Addition, Aug 1935 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-8)
  - Pulaski - Pulaski High School - Gymnasium Addition, Jan 1939 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-11)
  - Pulaski - Pico Terrace, Oct 1936 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-10)
  - Pulaski - Calfee Training- Addition, Feb 1939 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-12)
  - Pulaski - New River- Addition, July 1941 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-9)
  - Pulaski - Dublin School- Addition, n.d. (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-9)
  - Pulaski - Pulaski- Home Economics Cottage, Feb 1939 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-9)
  - Pulaski - Pulaski- Addition, May 1930 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-9)
  - Pulaski - Draper- Addition, July 1937 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-8)
  - Pulaski - Draper- Addition, July 192- (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-8)
  - Pulaski - Pico Terrace- Addition, May 1941 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-10)
  - Rappahannock - Sperryville- Addition, Jan 1936 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-13)
  - Rappahannock - Sperryville- Addition, Oct 1935 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-13)
  - Rappahannock - School At Washington- Addition, Feb 1934 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-13)
  - Rappahannock - School For Washington, July 1929 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-13)
  - Rappahannock - School At Washington- Addition, June 193- (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-13)
  - Richmond - School For Warsaw, May 1928 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-14)
  - Richmond - School For Warsaw, July 1938 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-14)
  - Richmond - School For Farnham, June 1932 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-15)
  - Richmond - School For Farnham, Feb 1938 (Folder 6, Folder 8-R-15)
  - Roanoke - Ogden, May 1930 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-5)
  - Roanoke - Canehurst, May 1932 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-6)
  - Roanoke - Garden City- Addition, May 1932 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-6)
  - Roanoke - Salem Grade School- Ventilating System, May 1931 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-5)
  - Roanoke - Starky, June 1928 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-3)
  - Roanoke - School For Catawba, June 1928 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-1)
  - Roanoke - School For Vinton, Aug 1927 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-1)
  - Roanoke - School For Bent Mountain, June 1930 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-3)
  - Roanoke - Mount Vernon (Four Room School), June 1926 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-4)
  - Roanoke - Fort Lewis- Addition, June 1941 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-2)
  - Roanoke - School For Fort Lewis, June 1928 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-2)
  - Roanoke - Oakland- Addition, May 1929 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-4)
  - Rockbridge - Effenger, Aug 1938 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-11)
  - Rockbridge - Goshen- Addition, Aug 1939 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-10)
  - Rockbridge - Goshen, March 193- (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-10)
  - Rockbridge - Glasgow, Nov 1938 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-9)
  - Rockbridge - Fairfield Shop, Jan 1942 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-9)
  - Rockbridge - Fairfield, Nov 1924 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-9)
  - Rockbridge - West Lexington- Addition, July 1928 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-8)
  - Rockbridge - Lexington (7 Room School), March 193- (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-8)
  - Rockbridge - Brownsburg Shop, June 1939 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-7)
  - Rockbridge - Brownsburg, Sept 1937 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-7)
  - Rockbridge - Fairfield- Addition, 1938 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-9)
  - Rockbridge - Natural Bridge Elementary, Oct 1938 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-11)
  - Rockingham - Linville (Edom)- Addition, May 1939 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-18)
  - Rockingham - Broadway - Agricultural School & Auditorium, April 1926 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-13)
  - Rockingham - Timber Ridge, July 1929 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-13)
  - Rockingham - Park, July 1929 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-13)
  - Rockingham - Bridgewater- Addition, June 1933 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-14)
  - Rockingham - Bridgewater- Alterations & Additions, Dec 1940 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-14)
  - Rockingham - McGaheysville - Auditorium & Gymnasium, April 1934 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-15)
  - Rockingham - Elkton - Auditorium - Gymnasium, April 1934 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-15)
  - Rockingham - Linwood Elementary- Auditorium & Gymnasium, Aug 1934 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-15)
  - Rockingham - Mount Clinton- Addition, April 1934 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-16)
  - Rockingham - Elktown, March 193- (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-17)
  - Rockingham - Port Republic- Addition, April 193- (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-12)
  - Rockingham - Dayton- Addition, April 1926 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-12)
  - Rockingham - Singer Glen- Addition, June 193- (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-12)
  - Rockingham - Keezletown- Addition, April 1934 (Folder 7, Folder 9-L-16)
  - Russell - Pine Creek- Addition, Aug 1932 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-2)
  - Russell - Temple Hill N.Y.A. Home Service, n.d. (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-7)
  - Russell - Temple Hill (At Castlewood)- Addition, Aug 1936 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-1)
  - Russell - Honaker- Addition, June 1941 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-2)
  - Russell - Honaker High School, Feb 1938 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-2)
  - Russell - School at Castlewood- Alterations & Additions, Oct 1943 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-3)
  - Russell - Lebanon High School- Addition, July 1935 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-4)
  - Russell - Lebanon High School- Vocational Building, Oct 1935 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-4)
  - Russell - Temple Hill (At Castlewood)- Addition, July 1940 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-5)
  - Russell - Cleveland High School- Gymnasium, Oct 1935 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-6)
  - Russell - Bellfast, n.d. (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-7)
  - Russell - Temple High School- Home Economics Cottage, June 1941 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-1)
  - Russell - Swords Creek - (6 Room School), May 1926 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-1)
  - Scott - Rye Cove, July 192- (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-8)
  - Shenandoah - St. Luke, June 193- (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-10)
  - Shenandoah - Edenburg, July 193- (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-11)
  - Shenandoah - Mt. Jackson, Nov 1938 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-12)
  - Shenandoah - Mt. Jackson- Alterations, Feb 1939 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-12)
  - Shenandoah - Strasburg, June 192- (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-9)
  - Smyth - McGrady, Sep 1932 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-16)
  - Smyth - Allison's Gap, Nov 1940 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-17)
  - Smyth - Sugar Grove, June 1940 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-17)
  - Smyth - Rich Valley- Addition, Aug 1938 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-13)
  - Smyth - Nebo, Oct 1934 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-17)
  - Smyth - Sugar Grove, June 194- (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-14)
  - Smyth - V.P.F. Marion- Strong Room, June 1944 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-13)
  - Smyth - Rich Valley, Aug 1926 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-13)
  - Smyth - Atkins, April 1930 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-15)
  - Smyth - Chilhowie, Aug 1929 (Folder 7, Folder 9-R-14)
  - Southampton - Franklin High School (3) Newsoms (2)- Addition, April 1936 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-2)
  - Southampton - Chancellor, Oct 1938 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-8)
  - Southampton - Franklin- Gymnasium & Agricultural Building, Oct 1935 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-8)
  - Southampton - Courtland Negro High School, Dec 193- (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-7)
  - Southampton - Franklin Negro High School, Sept 193- (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-6)
  - Southampton - Newsoms Colored School, Oct 1935 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-5)
  - Southampton - Franklin Grammar, May 1929 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-3)
  - Southampton - Ivor- Present High School, Jan 1926 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-2)
  - Southampton - Black Creek- Addition, July 192- (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-1)
  - Southampton - Four Room School & Auditorium, Aug 1925 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-1)
  - Southampton - Boykins, June 1933 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-4)
  - Spottsylvania - Home Economics, Aug 194- (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-10)
  - Spottsylvania - Central High School, Sept 193- (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-9)
  - Spottsylvania - Spottsylvania High School- Shop, June 194- (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-9)
  - Stafford - Temporary School - Near Quantico, Oct 1942 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-14)
  - Stafford - Falmouth Elementary, Aug 1924 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-11)
  - Stafford - Falmouth Agricultural Shop- Addition, Sept 1938 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-11)
  - Stafford - New Hope, June 194- (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-12)
  - Stafford - New Hope- Addition, Aug 1929 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-12)
  - Stafford - Stafford Colored High School- Alterations, July 1933 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-12)
  - Stafford - Stafford County Training, Oct 1938 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-13)
  - Stafford - Stafford County Training- Addition, Jan 1941 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-13)
  - Stafford - Falmouth Elementary, Aug 1924 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-11)
  - Stafford - Falmouth- Addition, June 193- (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-11)
  - Surry - Surry High School- Fire Escape, Oct 1936 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-15)
  - Surry - Surry County Training, Oct 1936 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-15)
  - Surry - Dendron High School- Fire Escape, Oct 1936 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-15)
  - Sussex - Stony Creek School- Addition, Oct 1938 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-19)
  - Sussex - Home Economics & Agriculture Building, June 1927 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-16)
  - Sussex - Jarratt- Alterations, Feb 1946 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-20)
  - Sussex - Jarratt- Addition, Oct 1938 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-20)
  - Sussex - Stony Creek High School, Sept 1940 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-19)
  - Sussex - Vocational Building- Addition, June 1945 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-18)
  - Sussex - Little Mill- Addition, July 1935 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-18)
  - Sussex - Sussex County Training School, June 1935 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-18)
  - Sussex - Garage For Waverly, Oct 1938 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-17)
  - Sussex - Waverly High School- Addition, Aug 1935 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-17)
  - Sussex - Waverly High School- - Alterations & Additions, Sept 1932 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-17)
  - Sussex - Waverly High School- Gymnasium, Aug 1935 (Folder 8, Folder 10-L-17)
  - Tazewell - Burks Garden, Feb 1937 (Folder 8, Folder 10-R-9)
  - Tazewell - Richlands High School, April 1941 (Folder 8, Folder 10-R-6)
  - Tazewell - Five Room School, July 1924 (Folder 8, Folder 10-R-1)
  - Tazewell - Red Ash, Aug 1927 (Folder 8, Folder 10-R-2)
  - Tazewell - Cedar Bluff Elementary, March 194- (Folder 8, Folder 10-R-11)
  - Tazewell - Gymnasium Addition & Alterations, March 1937 (Folder 8, Folder 10-R-10)
  - Tazewell - Dudley, Dec 1936 (Folder 8, Folder 10-R-8)
  - Tazewell - Richlands School- Addition, June 1938 (Folder 8, Folder 10-R-6)
  - Tazewell - Richlands- Agricultural Shop, Nov 1936 (Folder 8, Folder 10-R-6)
  - Tazewell - Tazewell High School (Now Jr. High), Feb 1932 (Folder 8, Folder 10-R-5)
  - Tazewell - Bishop, Sept 1931 (Folder 8, Folder 10-R-4)
  - Tazewell - North Tazewell, Sept 1931 (Folder 8, Folder 10-R-3)
  - Tazewell - Addition Logan Street - Bluefield, March 1937 (Folder 8, Folder 10-R-2)
  - Tazewell - Burks Garden- Vocational Building, Sept 1943 (Folder 8, Folder 10-R-1)
  - Tazewell - Raven- Addition, March 194- (Folder 8, Folder 10-R-1)
  - Tazewell - County Training School, Dec 1936 (Folder 8, Folder 10-R-7)
  - Warren - School At Front Royal- Addition, Feb 1927 (Folder 8, Folder 10-R-12)
  - Warren - Front Royal- Alterations, Aug 1938 (Folder 8, Folder 10-R-12)
  - Alexandria - Nursery School, Aug 1943 (Folder 9, Folder 12-L-9)
  - Alexandria - Falls Church- Alterations for Toilets, March 1932 (Folder 9, Folder 12-L-9)
  - Alexandria - Chinquapin, Apr 1942 (Folder 9, Folder 12-L-9)
  - Alexandria - Rosemont, Sep 1927 (Folder 9, Folder 12-L-9)
  - Alexandria - Falls Church- Addition, July 1936 (Folder 9, Folder 12-L-9)
  - Lexington - Lylburn Downing High School- Addition, April 194- (Folder 9, Folder 12-L-18)
  - Lexington - Lexington High School, March 192- (Folder 9, Folder 12-L-18)
  - Lynchburg - Chambersville, Sept 1926 (Folder 9, Folder 12-R-1)
  - Staunton - Colored School (Booker T. Washington), Oct 1935 (Folder 9, Folder 12-R-15)
  - Suffolk - Booker T. Washington- Addition, Oct 1935 (Folder 9, Folder 12-R-16)
  - Washington - William King High School- Addition, May 1925 (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-1)
  - Washington - Liberty Hill, n.d. (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-4)
  - Washington - North Bristol, Dec 1938 (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-4)
  - Washington - School At Meadowview- Addition, n.d. (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-3)
  - Washington - Abingdon High School- Lunch Room & Home Economics, March 194- (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-9)
  - Washington - Washington County Regional Trade School, May 1945 (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-8)
  - Washington - Central High School- Addition, March 1945 (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-7)
  - Washington - Greendale Shop- Addition, April 194- (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-6)
  - Washington - Greendale High School- Addition, May 1942 (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-6)
  - Washington - Abingdon- Shop Addition, July 1941 (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-5)
  - Washington - Abingdon- Shop, Oct 1938 (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-5)
  - Washington - School For Abingdon, June 1925 (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-2)
  - Waynesboro - School Layouts (Folder 9, Folder 12-R-17)
  - Waynesboro - Jackson Building (White Elementary), 1950 (Folder 9, Folder 12-R-17)
  - Waynesboro - Jackson Wilson Jr. High School - Kitchen, 1952 (Folder 9, Folder 12-R-17)
  - Waynesboro - Colored High School, 1950 (Folder 9, Folder 12-R-17)
  - Waynesboro - Jackson Wilson & Wenonah, 1949 (Folder 9, Folder 12-R-17)
  - Waynesboro - Wayne Hills (White Elementary), 1951 (Folder 9, Folder 12-R-17)
  - Waynesboro - Shenandoah Heights (White Elementary), 1950 (Folder 9, Folder 12-R-17)
  - Waynesboro - Wenonan (White Elementary), 1950 (Folder 9, Folder 12-R-17)
  - Westmoreland - Colonial Beach School- Addition & Alterations, Oct 1935 (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-12)
  - Westmoreland - School For Montross, Feb 1931 (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-10)
  - Westmoreland - School For Oak Grove, May 1932 (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-11)
  - Westmoreland - Cople, Jan 1945 (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-13)
  - Westmoreland - Hague- Addition, May 1936 (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-13)
  - Williamsburg - Mathew High School- Miscellaneous Alterations & Additions, 1943-1945 (Folder 9, Folder 12-R-18)
  - Williamsburg - Standard 6 Room School, Feb 1923 (Folder 9, Folder 12-R-18)
  - Williamsburg - Bruton Heights.- Alterations to Coal Room (Folder 9, Folder 12-R-18)
  - Winchester - Winchester Grammar, Feb 1930 (Folder 9, Folder 12-R-20)
  - Winchester - School For Winchester, March 192- (Folder 9, Folder 12-R-19)
  - Winchester - Douglas - Colored High School & Elementary, July 1950 (Folder 9, Folder 12-R-20)
  - Wythe - Agricultural Building Rural Retreat-Addition, Oct 1944 (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-16)
  - Wythe - North Austinville, Nov 1929 (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-15)
  - Wythe - Max Meadows- Addition, n.d. (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-14)
  - Wythe - Rural Retreat- Knitting Mill, Dec 1929 (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-14)
  - Wythe - School For Wytheville, April 1926 (Folder 9, Folder 11-L-14)
  - York - Poquoson- Alterations & Additions, Sept 1931 (Folder 9, Folder 11-R-12)
  - York - School For Yorktown, March 1928 (Folder 9, Folder 11-R-11)
  - York - Grammar School For Messick, Aug 1922 (Folder 9, Folder 11-R-10)
  - York - Oak Grove- Addition, May 1938 (Folder 9, Folder 11-R-10)
  - York - School For Poquoson, Aug 1943 (Folder 9, Folder 11-R-12)
  - York - Emergency School For Yorktown, July 1941 (Folder 9, Folder 11-R-11)
  - York - Yorktown School- Addition, March 1928 (Folder 9, Folder 11-R-11)
  - York - Poquoson- Alterations & Additions, July 1945 (Folder 9, Folder 11-R-12)
  - Miscellaneous - Miscellaneous Old Drawings, n.d. (Folder 10, Folder 13-R-3)
- Series II. Renderings/Photographs. (Box 11.)
  Consists of architectural renderings and photographs of school buildings. These include the original schools on the particular site, as well as newly constructed schools.
  There is no particular method of arrangement.
  - Renderings/Photographs - The President's Community School 1929/ Camp Rapidan Virginia/ Donated by President Hoover, 1929 (Folder 11, Folder 14)
  - Renderings/Photographs - Consolidated Colored High School/ Warrenton- Fauquier County, Virginia/ Smithey & Boynton Architects, Roanoke, Va., 1950 (Folder 11, Folder 14)
  - Renderings/Photographs - Proposed Sandston and Glen Echo School Buildings/ Henrico County Virginia/ Division of School Buildings/ State Department of Education, 1938 (Folder 11, Folder 14)
  - Renderings/Photographs - [Five Unidentified School Buildings- photographs by Bagby], n.d. (Folder 11, Folder 14)
  - Renderings/Photographs - Honacker High School/ Honacker, Virginia/ Smithey & Boynton Architects/ Roanoke, Va., n.d. (Folder 11, Folder 14)
  - Renderings/Photographs - Consolidated High School/ Rocky Mount, Franklin County, Virginia/ Smithey & Boynton Architects, Roanoke, Va., 1949 (Folder 11, Folder 14)
  - Renderings/Photographs - Thole Street Elementary School/ Norfolk, Virginia/ Oliver & Smith Architects, n.d. (Folder 11, Folder 14)
  - Renderings/Photographs - Washington Reed Elementary School/ Prince William Co. Va./ Frederick Tilp A.I.A Architect, Alexandria, Va., n.d. (Folder 11, Folder 14)
  - Renderings/Photographs - [Onancock High School- photo by Bagby], n.d. (Folder 11, Folder 14)
  - Renderings/Photographs - Martinsville High School, n.d. (Folder 11, Folder 14)
- Series III. Standard Plans. (Box 10-13., Reel 1837.)
  Consists of standardized plans for various types of school buildings and related structures.
  All drawings in box 10 within Series III. can be found on Miscellaneous Reel 1837.
  The drawings found in boxes 11-13 are not on film.
  - Standard Plans - Steel Stairways, Etc., n.d. (Folder 10, Folder 13-L-11)
  - Standard Plans - Septic Tanks, n.d. (Folder 10, Folder 13-L-11)
  - Standard Plans - Standard Home Economics and Agricultural Building, April 1920 (Folder 10, Folder 13-L-12)
  - Standard Plans - Standard Home Economics Cottages- 3-T, n.d. (Folder 10, Folder 13-L-12)
  - Standard Plans - Standard Home Economics Cottages- 2-T, Sept 194- (Folder 10, Folder 13-L-12)
  - Standard Plans - Standard Home Economics Cottages- 1-T, Feb 1940 (Folder 10, Folder 13-L-12)